Cierra Jarrell

Currently full time status, Assist patients - CNA VALLEY HEALTH HOME HEALTH

Stephens City, VA 22655 cierraebert3_wr6@indeedemail.com +1 540 303 8789

Compassionate and technically skilled in attending to patients in diverse healthcare settings. Reliable worker with the ability to learn new concepts and skills quickly. Backed by a solid work history, reputation as a team player and passion for helping others. Background includes experience caring for long term care and rehabilitation patients. I am striving for something more and completely willing to learn.

Work Experience

Currently full time status, Assist patients

CNA VALLEY HEALTH HOME HEALTH December 2014 to Present

with ADL's in the home to achieve the highest level of function for rehab. Responsible for setting up telehealth units. Check patient vital signs. Maintain electronic records of patient care on McKesson.

CNA - Certified Nursing Assistant

Valley Health - Winchester, VA Present

My duties include watching patients on a computer system for anything that may be harmful to themselves or the people around them such as falls, pulling of tubes and lines, or overall confusion.

CNA - Certified Nursing Assistant

CNA ENVOY OF WINCHESTER
November 2013 to December 2015

ASSIST RESIDENTS WITH ADLS. ENCOURAGE PARTICIPATION IN ACTIVITIES. MAINTAIN RECORDS OF PATIENT CARE. CHECK PATIENT VITAL SIGNS

Education

Bachelors of Science in Information Technology with a concentration in software development

University of Phoenix-Online Campus January 2020 to Present

Associate in Science

Blue Ridge Community and Technical College - Martinsburg, WV May 2016 to May 2018

Skills

- McKesson
- Vital Signs
- Epic
- Hospital Experience
- Medical Records
- EMR Systems
- Java (Less than 1 year)
- C++ (Less than 1 year)

Certifications and Licenses

CNA

CPR Certification

Assessments

Electronic health records: Best practices — Proficient

December 2020

Knowledge of EHR data, associated privacy regulations, and best practices for EHR use Full results: Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.

Additional Information

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Certified Nursing Assistant 2013- present
- Patient Care & Safety
- Vital Signs
- CPR (current)
- Skilled in McKesson software and charting
- Skilled in Microsoft office applications
- Type 30 WPM